There was a time when a cry for help was
only heard as far as your voice could travel.
Agora, as coisas são diferentes.
Now someone can be heard in a matter of seconds
all the way across the world.
A Internet tornou-se uma voz para os sem voz.
A way to shine awareness on hidden corruption
and it's changing the world.
[crowd chanting]
The whole world is watching!
Except that freedom isn't available to everyone.
Over a quarter of the world's population lives with government-imposed censorship
and that number is growing.
Politically sensitive sites like Facebook,
YouTube, Twitter e Google,
the exact sites that are bringing light to corruption and injustice,
are blocked.
Mas, você pode ajudar
utilizando o Lantern.
Lantern é um programa gratuito, seguro e protegido
that gives people internet access in places where access is denied.
It's software that circumvents government censorship.
Quando instala o Lantern no seu computador
está a providenciar uma nova rota de salvamento
para obter informação de entrada e  saída dos países censurados.
You are giving people a way out
a way to communicate.
Todos nós estamos conetados
agora, mais do que nunca.
With a few simple steps, you have the power
to provide equal access to the internet
and help change the world.
Irá?
Adira ao movimento.
Junte-se ao Lantern.