A fost o vreme cand un strigat de ajutor putea
fi auzit doar atat cat putea calatori vocea.
Acum lucrurile sunt diferite.
Acum cineva poate fi auzit in cateva secunde
de la un capat in altul al lumii.
Internetul a devenit vocea celor fara voce
Modul de a scoate la lumina faptele de coruptie
si sa schimbe lumea.
[multime scandand]
Toata lumea se uita!
Except that freedom isn't available to everyone.
Over a quarter of the world's population lives with government-imposed censorship
and that number is growing.
Politically sensitive sites like Facebook,
YouTube, Twitter, and Google,
the exact sites that are bringing light to corruption and injustice,
are blocked.
But you can help
by using Lantern.
Lantern is a safe and secure free software
that gives people internet access in places where access is denied.
It's software that circumvents government censorship.
When you install Lantern on your computer
you provide a new escape route
for getting information in and out of censored countries.
You are giving people a way out
a way to communicate.
All of us are connected
now more than ever.
With a few simple steps, you have the power
to provide equal access to the internet
and help change the world.
Will you?
Join the movement.
Join Lantern.